in this tutorial I'll be addressing a
在本教程中，我将介绍
bug that exists in the current version
当前版本中存在的错误
of inkscape where converting a stroke to
将笔划转换为
a path gives you a different result than
路径给您的结果不同于
what you expect and to show you what I
你所期待的，并向你展示我的
mean I have this simple fourpoint shape
我的意思是我有这个简单的四角形
that is a stroke and if I convert this
这是一个笔划，如果我把这个转换成
stroke to a path you can see what
划到一条你能看到的小路
happens we end up with a broken shape
碰巧我们最终得到了一个破碎的形状
now this is not what's supposed to
现在这不是我们应该做的
happen so I would imagine this is some
所以我会认为这是一些
kind of bug in the software now the
现在软件中有一种错误
inkscape team is usually good with
Inkscape团队通常擅长于
addressing these sorts of things so I'm
处理这类事情，所以我
sure this will be ironed out in the next
当然，这件事会在下一次解决的
update but in this tutorial I just want
更新，但在本教程中，我只想
to show you a simple fix for this so let
向你展示一个简单的解决方法，所以让我们
me press contrl Z to undo what I did
我按Ctrl Z来撤消我所做的
there what I'm going to do is I'm going
我要做的是我要去
to select the object and now before I
要选择该对象，现在在我
convert it to a stroke I will go to path
将其转换为笔划，我将转到Path
and I will select reverse and now if I
我会选择反转，现在如果我
go to path and select stroke to path you
转到路径并选择笔划来为您指定路径
can see we end up with the result as
可以看到我们最终的结果是
intended now I don't know much about the
打算现在我不太了解
back end of this software and how this
该软件的后端以及如何
sort of thing works but I would imagine
有点用，但我可以想象
it has something to do with how the
这与美国政府如何
start and end point of a path is defined
定义了路径的起点和终点
because the reverse function is normally
因为反向函数通常是
only used when we place text on a path
仅当我们将文本放置在路径上时使用
and we want to define whether the text
我们想要定义文本是否
goes on the outside of the path or the
走在小路的外面，或者
inside of the path but in this instance
在路径内，但在本例中
it's also useful here as well another
它在这里也很有用，还有另一个
thing you can do you can also flip the
你可以做的事情你也可以翻转
object so if I were to press the letter
反对，所以如果我按下这封信
H on my keyboard and flip it
在我的键盘上点击并翻转它
horizontally that will also work the
在水平方向上，这也将适用于
same way and I would imagine because it
同样的方式，我可以想象，因为它
reverses the path the same way path
以相同的方式反转路径
reverse does and then after that you
反向操作，然后在此之后
could just press h again and then it's
可以再按一次h然后它就
back to the starting point so that
回到起点，这样才能
should do it for today's video I just
今天的视频应该是这样的，我只是
wanted to get this fix out there in case
想把这件事公之于众，以防万一
you were encountering this problem and
您遇到了这个问题，
it was frustrating you if you have any
如果你有任何，那你会很沮丧
questions leave a comment below and as
问题在下面留下评论和作为
always thanks for watching
始终感谢观看